I don't give a [__] what you think about
me. See all these haters talk. They fly
like me. Are the only rainy days where
you live?
It's funny when we talk that you're
always so nice. Let me be on my back and
pull out your lights. Do you really have
nothing else to do?
So when she said that she said that
someone know who told them rumors that
nobody
know I don't give a [__] what you think
about me. Maybe if you're mad count to 1
2 3. Maybe if you're sad trying to love
call me cuz I don't care anymore.
It's always easy that she said that some
told them rumors that don't bother me.
And so he said that she said that
someone oh told them rumors that don't
bother me.
No I don't give a [__] what you think
about me. Maybe if you're mad one two
three. Maybe if you're sad try to not
call me cuz I don't care anymore. Know I
don't give a [__] what you think about
me. Maybe if you're mad to one, two,
three. Maybe if you sad, try to not call
me cuz I don't care anymore.